<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<products>
    <golf>
        <code>11AE56</code>
        <stock>12</stock>
        <name>Taylormade Qi10</name>
        <description>The higher the inertia the more forgiving the driver. Introducing the all-new Qi10 Max driver, experience TaylorMade speed with the forgiveness of 10K inertia.</description>
        <price>799.99</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <flex>Stiff</flex>
        <righthanded>true</righthanded>
    </golf>
    <golf>
        <code>11AE60</code>
        <stock>5</stock>
        <name>Taylormade Qi Iron</name>
        <description>It’s no surprise that golfers tend to miss to the right. That’s why the Qi irons are engineered to eliminate frustrating fades and guide your shots confidently to the target. Unlike other game improvement irons that actually favor a right miss, ours are meticulously designed for precision and control because straight distance is the best distance.</description>
        <price>1399.99</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <flex>Stiff</flex>
        <righthanded>true</righthanded>
    </golf>
    <golf>
        <code>11AE70</code>
        <stock>22</stock>
        <name>TP Black Juno</name>
        <description>The Juno™ shape is offered in two unique hosel options giving players two toe hang options. Inspired by Collin Morikawa, the long hosel produces 27° of toe hang that helps deliver a more face balanced performance profile while maintaining the aesthetic and alignment benefits of a traditional L-neck blade. The L-neck hosel and traditional blade shape generate 38° of toe hang, delivering a putter that best fits players who create heavy face rotation throughout the putting motion.</description>
        <price>269.99</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <flex>Regular</flex>
        <righthanded>true</righthanded>
    </golf>
    <golf>
        <code>12AE454</code>
        <stock>23</stock>
        <name>Callaway X Club</name>
        <description>Very stiff, drives long</description>
        <price>345.88</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <flex>Stiff</flex>
        <righthanded>true</righthanded>
    </golf>
    <snowboard>
        <code>11SE00</code>
        <stock>39</stock>
        <name>Burton Feelgood Camber</name>
        <description>Like a technicolor dream, the Feelgood is the magic carpet to make your dreams come true. Every drip and color in the graphic represents terrain you can ride. Just like the board's spirited ride and all-mountain versatility make every day on snow memorable.</description>
        <price>559.99</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <length>146</length>
        <goofy>false</goofy>
    </snowboard>
    <snowboard>
        <code>11SE10</code>
        <stock>33</stock>
        <name>Burton Custom Camber</name>
        <description>All aboard the rocket ship that is the Burton Custom. This classic board is standard issue for all our troops, so it gets fun, fast-looking art that everyone can appreciate, just like the board's trusted ride.</description>
        <price>615.99</price>
        <onsale>true</onsale>
        <length>166</length>
        <goofy>false</goofy>
    </snowboard>
    <snowboard>
        <code>11SE00</code>
        <stock>36</stock>
        <name>Burton X Camber</name>
        <description>This season's Custom X ties it all together with a floating monolith-inspired graphic that explores the furthest reaches of space in search of the perfect line. Foil details and glowing ink change with the light and angle to make the imagery hum. Just like the boards aggressive flex brings every line to life.</description>
        <price>769.99</price>
        <onsale>false</onsale>
        <length>162</length>
        <goofy>true</goofy>
    </snowboard>
</products>